<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string-array name="chuck_jokes_array">
        <item>When Chuck Norris was born he drove his mom home from the hospital.</item>
        <item>Chuck Norris has a diary. Its called the Guinness Book of World Records</item>
        <item>Chuck Norris threw a grenade and killed 50 people, then it exploded</item>
        <item>Chuck Norris does not worry about high gas prices. His vehicles run on fear</item>
        <item>Chuck Norris counted to infinity. Twice</item>
        <item>Chuck Norris can kill two stones with one bird.</item>
        <item>When a zombie apocalypse starts, Chuck Norris does not try to survive. The zombies do</item>
        <item>There once was a street called Chuck Norris, but the name was changed for public safety because nobody crosses Chuck Norris and lives.</item>
        <item>Big foot claims he saw Chuck Norris.</item>
        <item>Chuck Norris can hear sign language</item>
        <item>It is considered a great accomplishment to go down Niagara Falls in a wooden barrel. Chuck Norris can go up Niagara Falls in a cardboard box.</item>
        <item> Once a cobra bit Chuck Norris leg. After five days of excruciating pain, the cobra died</item>
        <item>Chuck Norris does not cheat death. He wins fair and square</item>
        <item>Chuck Norris beat the sun in a staring contest</item>
        <item>Giraffes were created when Chuck Norris uppercutted a horse.</item>
        <item>When the Boogeyman goes to sleep every night he checks his closet for Chuck Norris</item>
        <item>Chuck Norris will never have a heart attack even a heart isnt foolish enough to attack Chuck Norris</item>
        <item>Chuck Norris once went to mars. Thats why there are no signs of life</item>
        <item>Chuck Norris is the reason Waldo is hiding.</item>
        <item>Jack was nimble, Jack was quick, but Jack still could not dodge Chuck Norris roundhouse kick</item>
        <item>Chuck Norris can strangle you with a cordless phone.</item>
        <item>There is no theory of evolution, just a list of creatures Chuck Norris allows to live.</item>
        <item>Chuck Norris calendar goes straight from March 31st to April 2nd. No one fools Chuck Norris.</item>
        <item>Chuck Norris once fought superman. The loser had to wear his underwear over his pants.</item>
        <item>Chuck Norris can kill your imaginary friends.</item>
        <item>Chuck can set ants on fire with a magnifying glass. At night.</item>
        <item>Chuck Norris makes onions cry</item>
        <item>The reason the Holy Grail has never been recovered is because nobody is brave enough to ask Chuck Norris to give up his favourite coffee mug.</item>
        <item>Chuck Norris is the only person that can punch a cyclops between the eye.</item>
    </string-array>
    
</resources>